Without a doubt.
We've always said
We've always
Tesla is not
an auto company.
auto company.
It is actually
the convergence of
is actually
three of the
platforms I mentioned,
platforms I
so robotics,
energy storage,
and AI. Each
one of those
AI. Each
technologies has
its own
S-curve, and now
they're feeding each
they're feeding
other, and we're
seeing that in
seeing that
robotaxis. Robotaxis,
we believe,
will account for
90% of Tesla's
90% of
valuation by the
valuation by
end of the
decade. We're in
print at 2,600.
at 2,600.
That includes
nothing for Optimus
robots.
And we're beginning
to understand
we're beginning
how quickly
Tesla is moving
on that
front. Why?
Mm. Because it's
Mm. Because
the convergence of
the same three
technologies- Mm-hmm robotics,
Mm-hmm robotics,
energy storage,
and AI.
So I think
that price target,
price target,
obviously, if Optimus
obviously, if
is successful,
and we believe
it will be.
we believe
We think that
humanoid robots is
humanoid robots
evolving into
a $26
trillion
opportunity, half
in the home,
half in manufacturing
in manufacturing
plants.